voxcinemas.com 2013-04-03

# VOX Cinemas Privacy Policy

## Internet privacy policy statement

VOX Cinemas is committed to ensuring your personal information is protected. VOX Cinemas understands and appreciates you are concerned about your privacy and about the confidentiality and security of information we may collect about you. This will explain how we treat your personal information.

## The information we collect about you

We collect personal data such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone/fax numbers etc., when submitted by visitors. These data are used for VOX Cinemas' internal marketing, promotional and information purposes. By submitting this information, you consent to such use.

VOX Cinemas only collects personal information by fair, lawful and non-intrusive means.

## How we use your information and whom we may disclose it to

The information that we collect about you is used to help us provide you with an information and entertainment service and with offers, competitions etc from time to time. In the future it may also help us to assist you in acquiring the goods that VOX Cinemas sells.

The information we collect from you is strictly confidential. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease the information stored in our databases to any third parties. VOX Cinemas does not collect sensitive information unless the individual has consented, it is required by law, or in other special specified circumstances, for example, relating to individual or public health or safety.

VOX Cinemas only uses or discloses information for the purpose for which it was collected.

## Access and contact

Any personal information that we collect about customers including email addresses will be kept in a database which is accessible only by those authorized to perform normal daily tasks such as updating addresses and renewing membership.

## Our security procedures

Once we receive personal information from you, we take all reasonable steps to ensure that all information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, up to date and stored in a secure environment and accessed only by authorized persons.

## Where cookies fit in

Cookies are pieces of information that a website can transfer to an individual's computer hard drive for record keeping. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many websites use them. Cookies are useful for facilitating a user's access to and use of a site. They allow us to track usage patterns and compile data that can help us improve our services to you. Cookie information is used in aggregated form - we do not use it to identify you as an individual. However, if you do not wish any information to be collected through the use of cookies you can change the functions in most web browsers to deny the cookie feature. You can also delete cookies from your hard drive at any time.

## Contact information

We take the privacy of your information seriously and it is important that you understand how we manage your personal information. If you have any questions or comments in relation to this Privacy Policy Statement please contact us at feedback@voxcinemas.com or by mail addressed to: The CEO, VOX Cinemas, P. O. Box 32625 Dubai, UAE. Fax: +97142940223 Your personal information can also be amended or deleted on-line through the website.

## General

Links from this site may take you to sites not covered by this Privacy Policy and we advise you to check the applicable privacy practices yourself. VOX Cinemas has no responsibility or liability for these practices.

If you need any more information please contact us.

This policy may be modified from time to time.
